<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="about_help">
        &lt;b&gt;HELP&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        ReLaunchX is a versatile reading programs launcher and system-wide shell for Onyx Boox Max.
        It is a continuation of ReLaunch 1.3.8 made for Nook Simple Touch (also supported by Sony PRS-T1).&lt;br&gt;
        It is assumed that the user library is organized in an ordered structure
        of folders and files have names of books that match their names.&lt;br&gt;
        ReLaunchX supports flexible configuration of many on-screen buttons for quick
        access to certain features of the program and run third party applications.&lt;br&gt;
        Non-obvious possibilities:&lt;br&gt;
        - Some functions of the program available only with run as a desktop shell for system.&lt;br&gt;
        - Some functions require a device with root-access, or only implemented for
        Nook Simple Touch (you will receive appropriate notice).&lt;br&gt;
        - On-screen scrolling buttons support double click to navigate to the specified
        number of percents in list and long-click to quickly move to the end (beginning) of the file list.
        This feature often will not work properly, be careful (you need to enable it in settings).&lt;br&gt;
        - If you open with the button, for example, the second-to-read book, it will be after the opening of the first.
        Thus, you will start in round fashion two (three, etc., depending on the configuration), the last-readed books.&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="about_appr">
        &lt;b>APPRECIATIONS&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        - ReLaunch project&lt;br>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://github.com/yiselieren/ReLaunch">https://github.com/yiselieren/ReLaunch&lt;/a>&lt;br>
        - Android Asset Studio (icons)&lt;br>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://romannurik.github.io/AndroidAssetStudio/index.html">https://romannurik.github.io/AndroidAssetStudio/index.html&lt;/a>&lt;br>
        - CoolReader Engine project (Eink support code)&lt;br> 
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://sourceforge.net/projects/crengine/">http://sourceforge.net/projects/crengine/&lt;/a>&lt;br>
        - Interactivemania (icons pack)&lt;br>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.interactivemania.com/">http://www.interactivemania.com/&lt;/a>&lt;br>
        &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.defaulticon.com/">http://www.defaulticon.com/&lt;/a>&lt;br> 
        &lt;br>
        </string>
    <string name="whats_new" translatable="false">
        &lt;b>CHANGELOG&lt;/b>&lt;br>
        &lt;a href="https://github.com/Leszek111/ReLaunchX/">https://github.com/Leszek111/ReLaunchX/&lt;/a>&lt;br>
    </string>

</resources>